Dmitry Artamonov

Full Stack Developer, Backend Developer

Kiryat Motzkin | 535-002162 | <u>artamonov2009@gmail.com</u> <u>Github</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

SUMMARY

As a Full Stack Developer, I possess valuable skills in Python and JavaScript programming, with a particular focus on projects with complex Backend components. My expertise also extends to API development and efficient data processing, where I have successfully automated pricing strategies and optimized product management by integrating CMS with external services. Additionally, I have honed my skills in creating chat-bots for Telegram. I am constantly learning and prefer projects that challenge and develop me as a developer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, Django, Django REST, Javascript, Node.js, React, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL, Git, MS Excel

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Dynamic prices for marketplaces - Github | (Python, OOP, API)

Changes prices of products on marketplaces to achieve maximum profit

- Utilized JSON Web Tokens and local Storage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Get with API and JSON sales data and analyze it for each product
- Change prices on marketplace with API
- Save all changes to JSON and XLS for for user convenience

DnD Bestiary Telegram Bot - Github ((Python, OOP, API))

Gives user information card of a monster from DND Bestiary

- Handle user's request, search monster info in JSON file and return information and picture in a user-friendly format
- Dice rolls and return monster's health points according to DnD system

EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder and CEO: ZEERO.ru

St. Petersburg, Russia | 2017 - Present

- Created successful online store from scratch
- Designed dynamic prices system (Python + API) to ensure maximum profit of sales on marketplaces
- Organized the order delivery and payment process, integrated with delivery services and payment gateways
- Implemented API connection with marketplaces
- Created data processing system to load marketplaces sales reports

Projects and Campaign Lead, Head of regional office: Greenpeace Russia St. Petersburg, Russia | 2001 - 2019

- Planned, executed, and monitored diverse sustainability and conservation initiatives in collaboration with stakeholders
- Conducted environmental impact assessments, facilitated community engagement, and secured funding for projects
- Leaded teams up to 50 employers and volunteers to achieve project's goals

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Tel Aviv, Israel | 03/2023 - 08/2023

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Generation Python for professionals Generation Python for advanced Russia | 12/2022 - Present Russia | 09/2022 - 12/2022

BeeGeek School

Radio-Electronics Engineer, BA

Saint-Petersburg University of Telecommunications

St. Petersburg, Russia

1999

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent, Russian - Native